So now we have sliced our mirliton in half again chayote in some parts of the country.
We have our water coming to a boil right here and we want to season this with some salt.
So give just a few grinds.
The mirlitons will pick up a lot of salt flavor so don't go over board.
Almost like what you would do with pasta go ahead and do it that way.
Then we are going to leave this seed in because we are going to remove this later.
This is going to be our chauffeur in the beautiful stuffing that we would make.
So just go ahead and put that right into the boiling water.
This is going to go about 30-40 minutes until they are fork tender.
So what you want to do is just keep a eye on them.
About 30 minutes range, maybe put a knife or a fork in there just to see if it is tender and we would show you what you do after that.